2026-03-18 | d096981 | solved all bugs related to minimax
2026-03-17 | 2e96175 | AI can take over in two player mode
2026-03-17 | 60cf4a7 | added buttons to make game navigation easy
2026-03-16 | 7201ea5 | made some more improvements, but still not fast enough
2026-03-16 | 98bcf63 | in the same
2026-03-16 | a19c87a | improvements but check classify_tile
2026-03-16 | 222375d | made massive performamnce improvements, but need to make sure the new classify_tiles in nonagabitboard works correctly
2026-03-15 | 8a6e1d5 | switched to vs ide
2026-03-15 | 1dc5f1b | made improvements but still more to do. converted some files to pure C
2026-03-13 | 248782e | still fixing AI
2026-03-13 | 1a29c7c | not much
2026-03-13 | fae174d | Still doesnt run, but we might not be far. Still making the two player mode work
2026-03-13 | ef869b1 | removed cloning and made the cost function theoretically faster
2026-03-12 | c8c6999 | setup aire
2026-03-12 | bbb8dd7 | rectified a file name
2026-03-12 | 0c73c01 | job
2026-03-12 | ff8787f | updated compiler to support linux
2026-03-12 | f50eee3 | job
2026-03-12 | 83723d9 | Stop tracking conda_env directory
2026-03-12 | 28927f5 | python script updated
2026-03-12 | be5bdf3 | Aire
2026-03-12 | cfbc955 | setup aire script
2026-03-12 | 4d04d59 | just a test commit
2026-03-10 | b45f7be | added strategies and the GA now runs
2026-03-10 | 940b5e8 | created the genetic algorithm class
2026-03-10 | af1fed1 | robust cost function and some optimization
2026-02-27 | e08098d | created AI class in cython and implemented incomplete cost function. fixed some issues with minmax
2026-02-27 | cf3c117 | created AI class in cython and implemented incomplete cost function. fixed some issues with minmax
2026-02-26 | 88ff8e2 | added some comments to guide the development of the cost function
2026-02-26 | b65b781 | doubled the depth for the same execution time, implementing a-b pruning and cython
2026-02-26 | c21759d | optimizing using snakeviz
2026-02-18 | a11ef69 | Implemented minmax, but it is extremely slow for d>2 and cost function returns a constant so basically nonexistant
2026-02-18 | d510499 | change the name of two files
2026-02-10 | ebb82f5 | win detection implemented
2026-02-09 | b47c882 | removed axel'nonaga implementation, forgot it was still here
2026-02-09 | 51068f5 | fixed the tile bug
2026-02-09 | 597a30d | we can move tiles but there is a slight bug with tiles with 3 disconnectedd neighbors. previous piece bugs were fixed
2026-02-09 | 8d56f8a | can move pieces, but discovered a bug with piece moving
2026-02-06 | 5c66b51 | when a tile is clicked on, it shows possible moves for it.
2026-02-06 | 23112f9 | hovering on a piece makes it;s possible moves show
2026-01-30 | b180056 | can detect mouse events, but cant move anything yet
2026-01-27 | 4b15f7b | we are displaying the nonaga board, but the board cannot change yet
2026-01-22 | 0de492a | Finished nonaga_island and the init of nonaga_board
2025-12-22 | ff709c7 | implemented the updated tiles function that will be used for add and remove tiles
2025-12-22 | a809f08 | put some order in the files, updated the gitignore and created the architecture of the project
2023-02-18 | a0ee825 | Change link to nonaga.com
2023-02-01 | ad811a5 | Add type annotations and text wrapping
2023-01-31 | 8675667 | Add readme
2023-01-31 | b20ae15 | Add link to source code
2023-01-31 | 4c94706 | Preparing for v1
2023-01-31 | 2f30a8f | handle window resize
2023-01-30 | 4329c6a | add credits
2023-01-30 | 54a95a0 | Add page title
2023-01-27 | ae2fc27 | Preparing for v1
2023-01-27 | 9ced877 | Remove Evergreen migrations
2023-01-27 | 4c4ff84 | Delete room if left empty
2023-01-26 | 0627e41 | Initial model
2023-01-26 | db15601 | Preparing for v2
2023-01-25 | 7c757a4 | Evergreen migrations V1 -> V2
2023-01-25 | f4d2dd3 | Remove debug values
2023-01-25 | 4fbd54b | Fix leaving room
2023-01-25 | a88c7e4 | Clean subscriptions and client state
2023-01-25 | bc26826 | Various tasks: replay button, leave room if not found, rename backend room
2023-01-23 | f74bf6f | Refacto room messages
2023-01-22 | a7df0b1 | introduce Game.getWinner, remove winnerview
2023-01-18 | 5cffe91 | Preparing for v1
2023-01-18 | 003c865 | Remove last debug
2023-01-18 | 2764503 | Only current player can move
2023-01-18 | c1e40f7 | Handle urls
2023-01-17 | b8b4803 | Display gameWidget
2023-01-16 | 623b491 | Flatten backend and frontend state (rooms)
2023-01-15 | 8864589 | Change waiting message
2023-01-14 | 8f8b777 | Flatten frontendroom type, id userId to other users
2023-01-13 | fe83f37 | Refacto Inside state: turn into record
2023-01-13 | 47e74b2 | Refacto client state, refacto room state out of backend
2023-01-12 | fea99e2 | Start game is broadcasted correctly
2023-01-09 | 8f35564 | Fix join room, room full
2023-01-07 | a504537 | Player assignment, breaks room full error
2023-01-05 | ffc0b1c | Refactor room opaque types, add client rooms
2023-01-05 | 4697633 | Refactor onDisconnect
2023-01-04 | fe5de4c | Synchrnize room presence between clients
2023-01-04 | de6d1ff | Put rooms and roomId into opaque types
2023-01-04 | 55f225d | Add room join debug info to front page
2023-01-04 | 24628b3 | Add component file, handle joined room message on frontend
2023-01-03 | adb6cee | Handle client join or create request
2023-01-02 | f3773c8 | Fix column usage, center join button
2023-01-02 | 4bdb4ab | Add room selection form
2022-12-28 | eb1401c | frontend play
